<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zee Shopping</string>

    <string name="first_slide">Choose Your Products</string>
    <string name="second_slide">Fast Delivery</string>
    <string name="third_slide">Good Service</string>
    <string name="description">An Amzood app with good service and fast delivery is a digital platform that enables customers to shop for products online, place orders, and have them delivered to their doorstep quickly and efficiently.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="New">new</string>
    <string name="product_name">Product Name</string>
    <string name="_90">90</string>
    <string name="price">Price: $</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">Close navigation</string>
    <string-array name="spinnerlist">
        <item> This is question </item>
        <item>This is answer</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="terms_conditions_content">
    <![CDATA[
         These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of our app.\n\n
        1. Acceptance of Terms: By using our app, you agree to comply with these terms and conditions.\n\n
        2. Account Registration: To access certain features, you may need to create an account. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account information.\n\n
        3. Product Information: We strive to provide accurate product information, but we do not warrant the completeness, reliability, or accuracy of any product details on our app.\n\n
        4. Ordering and Payment: When placing an order, you agree to provide accurate and complete information. Payment processing is handled securely, but we are not liable for any unauthorized access to your payment information.\n\n
        5. Shipping and Delivery: We aim to deliver products within the specified timeframes, but we cannot guarantee exact delivery dates. Delivery may be subject to additional charges.\n\n
        6. Returns and Refunds: Our return and refund policy governs the process for returning and receiving refunds for products purchased through our app.\n\n
        7. Intellectual Property: All intellectual property rights, including trademarks and copyrights, associated with our app are owned by us.\n\n
        8. Limitation of Liability: We are not liable for any damages or losses arising from your use of our app, including but not limited to direct, indirect, incidental, or consequential damages.\n\n
        9. Governing Law: These terms and conditions are governed by the laws of your jurisdiction.\n\n
        By using our app, you agree to these terms and conditions in their entirety. If you do not agree with any part of these terms, please refrain from using our app.\n\n
        If you have any questions or concerns about our terms and conditions, please contact us.\n
    ]]>
</string>




</resources>